fyple.biz 2019-05-21

# Privacy policy - Fyple

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using Contact form. At www.fyple.biz, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.fyple.biz and how it is used. 

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our services, including those offered through our website, contact form and email.

The personal data we would like to collect and process on you are:

  * Your name 
  * Your email address 
  * Your postcode 
  * Your company address 
  * Your phone number 
  * A password of your choosing 

## Consent

By consenting to this privacy notice you are giving us permission to process your personal data specifically for the purposes identified.

www.fyple.biz will NOT pass on your personal data to third parties without first obtaining your consent except where there is clear Legitimate Interest.

## Your rights as a data subject

At any point while we are in possession of or processing your personal data, you, the data subject, have the following rights:

  * Right of access – you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. 
  * Right of rectification – you have a right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete. 
  * Right to be forgotten – in certain circumstances, you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records. 
  * Right to restriction of processing – where certain conditions apply to have a right to restrict the processing. 
  * Right of portability – you have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation. 
  * Right to object – you have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing. 
  * Right to object to automated processing, including profiling – you also have the right to be subject to the legal effects of automated processing or profiling. 
  * Right to judicial review: You have the right to complain as outlined below. 

All of the above requests will be forwarded on should there be a third party involved in the processing of your personal data. 

In order for us to provide you with a requested product or service, we need to collect personal data for correspondence purposes and detailed service provision. In any event, we are committed to ensuring that the information we collect and use is appropriate for this purpose, and does not constitute an invasion of your privacy. 

In terms of being contacted for marketing purposes, www.fyple.biz would contact you for additional consent.

www.fyple.biz will process (collect, store and use) the information you provide in a manner compatible with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We will endeavour to keep your information accurate and up to date, and not keep it for longer than is necessary. 

Links: We may link to third party services, like a business’s URL. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third party services.

## Security

We use various safeguards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## How you can contact us

If you would like to exercise your data protection rights or if you are unhappy with how we have handled your personal data, you may contact us by: 

  * email: support@fyple.biz; 
  * submitting a message through our online contact form Contact form

## Cookies Policy

A cookie is a small text file which is placed onto your computer (or other electronic device) when you access our Site.

We may use cookies on our Site for a number of reasons, all of which are designed to improve your experience of using it. Cookies allow you to navigate around our Site better and enable us to tailor and improve our Site by saving your preferences and understanding your use of it.

#### Strictly Necessary Cookies

A cookie falls into this category if it is essential to the operation of our Site, supporting functions such as logging in. 

#### Analytics Cookies

It is important for us to understand how you use our Site, for example, how efficiently you are able to navigate around it, and what features you use. Analytics cookies enable us to gather this information, helping us to improve our Site and your experience of it.

#### How you can control cookies

Internet browsers normally accept cookies by default. You can change these settings if you wish, however please be aware that this is not generally a per-site setting and will prevent all websites from using cookies, not just ours. Please also be aware that by disabling cookies in your browser, you may impair the functionality of our Site. The links below provide instructions on how to control cookies in all mainstream browsers:

Internet Explorer – [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11);

Firefox – [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences);

Chrome – [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&hlrm=en);

Setari cookie în Safari – [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac);

Edge – [Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy);

Opera – [Opera](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/);

For more information about cookies, please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) (this is an external link and we are not responsible for its content).

Fyple may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Business Listing or account username, or by placing a prominent notice on the site.
